Greetings, Princess Consort Ling.
How can I help you?
Is Prince Ling here?
Prince Ling has gone hunting for a few days.
If it's urgent, just tell me.
I wonder if Your Highness
knows what this is.
Western Regions Ice Silkworm Silk.
Your Highness is indeed very knowledgeable.
This kind of Ice Silkworm Silk is very rare.
Does Your Highness have any in the mansion?
The Ice Silkworm Silk quilts in my mansion
are all made of this.
By the way,
there's an artisan in Fangzhou
who is exceptionally good at making this kind of Ice Silkworm Silk.
He does it even better than the craftsmen in Chang'an.
Where is this person?
Five miles west of the Xiguan Town gate,
there is a silkworm breeder named Wu.
Five miles to the west.
It perfectly matches the time of death.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Are you coming or not?
Let's go.
We've walked ten miles,
and where is the silkworm breeder?
Could Princess Consort Ling be lying to us?
I don't think
she would lie to us.
You were looking at her quite closely just now.
Did I?
When we're out investigating a case, focus on the case.
Don't always let your imagination run wild.
I'm hungry.
There's a shop ahead,
let's get something to eat.
Anyone here?
He says
we should taste the yellow wine of Fangzhou.
You know sign language too?
You know what they say,
you can never have too many skills.
Sir,
are you a silkworm breeder?
He says he runs a restaurant
and additionally
breeds silkworms.
Sir,
are the silkworms you breed
different from others?
I see they're all covered with black cloth.
He says
his silkworms here are very precious.
They require a very low temperature
to spin silk that is fine and cold.
Are they Ice Silkworms?
He says no.
How could an old, lonely man like him have such ability?
Sir,
is your surname Wu?
He says his surname is Zhang.
Is there a silkworm breeder named Wu around here?
He says if you walk a mile ahead,
there's a family named Wu.
They breed silkworms very well.
Thank you.
Is it this person?
We'll know when we see.
Let's go.
Xuanji Diagram.
Hong Niangzi.
I could tell early on
that there's something wrong with you.
A little girl's hands
actually have sword calluses.
The recent murders by Hong Niangzi,
you did them all, didn't you?
You shouldn't speak nonsense.
The ice silkworm thread, the Xuanji map, the corpse acupuncture,
all of these match up.
Here
is the primary scene where you murdered Chen Wenyuan
and Liu Rumei.
Then you hung them on the intertwined branches.
You used the story of Hongniangzi
to cover up the fact of your crime.
Right?
Since you found out,
then today,
dead or alive, you're staying here.
Who exactly are you?
Why did you kill so many people?
He said
he had a fetish.
One day, I fished out a female corpse in red from the river.
It was the famous Hongniangzi.
I liked her corpse,
so I used ice silkworm thread to delay the decay.
Until one day,
A pair of star-crossed lovers
passed by here while eloping.
From their conversation, I learned
the man was the son of Hongniangzi's unfaithful lover.
A brilliant plan came to mind.
I drugged them,
killed Chen Wenyuan,
raped Liu Rumei,
and took their money.
Then,
I used the legend of Hongniangzi to cover it up.
I didn't expect
so many people would believe it.
This corpse,
could it be...
He said this is Hongniangzi.
He liked her tattoo.
That you were able to trace it here
really
exceeds my expectations.
Since you are here,
let Hongniangzi
kill again.
Oh no.
What do we do, Shen Zhao?
Whistle.
Stop joking.
Why blow a whistle now?
Blow the whistle for help.
Fire!
Put it out!
This way.
Lord Su,
Young Master Shen,
are you alright?
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Quick.
Su Yao of our county office
is brave and intelligent.
Handling matters with perseverance,
she cracked the Hongniangzi case,
dispelling rumors for our Fangzhou.
Her contribution is undeniable.
Promoted by one rank,
rewarded with a hundred taels of silver.
Zhang Chao, Li Meng,
rewarded equally.
Hey,
what about us?
Thank you, Lord Su.
Thank you.
Cheers!
Come on.
From now on, we are all brothers.
Cheers!
Come on.
Lord Su is really busy every day.
Still keeping a straight face at a time like this.
I just feel something is wrong.
Like what?
Why did Zhang Chao and Li Meng
happen to pass by here?
Wasn't there a report?
Then why did
the candlestick happen to light the red string?
Go. Hurry up.
Hurry.
Some things
just get more complicated the more you think about them.
We might as well just get drunk.
Where is Wu Shan's body?
I want to take a look.
Sister.
You've drunk the entire yamen under the table.
What else do you want to see?